<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi, Everyone! on Thijs Overmeer</title>
    <link>https://thijsovermeer.nl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hi, Everyone! on Thijs Overmeer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thijsovermeer.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 4: Regression analysis</title>
      <link>https://thijsovermeer.nl/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thijsovermeer.nl/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Building a notebook in which different algorithms are used to predict the housing prices based on a dataset from Kaggle. I used both a random forest model and a keras neural network. In the end, the random forest model worked significantly better than the neural network. This project was aimed to increase my skills in building regression models as I had not done this before. With the help of example Kaggle notebooks, I learned a lot from this project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3: Building a convolutional network to classify images.</title>
      <link>https://thijsovermeer.nl/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thijsovermeer.nl/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>I build a convolutional neural network, that could classify images into 10 different classes. The thing that I am most proud of is that I managed to visualize the parts where the neural network paid attention to. This can be seen in the next picture.
  The parts that are red are the parts where the convolutional layer paid attention to. The following code was used for this implementation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Kubeflow</title>
      <link>https://thijsovermeer.nl/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thijsovermeer.nl/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Building a kubeflow pipeline for predicting the number in the mnist dataset. This project was carried out during my first semester at JADS.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: BAS Trucks</title>
      <link>https://thijsovermeer.nl/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thijsovermeer.nl/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>In the first semester, while studying at JADS, we made a dashboard for BAS trucks, which could predict in which certain vehicles were going to be sold. Also using an API, we created a dashboard for BAS Trucks where it could specify vehicle characteristics and based on this the model would predict how likely a vehicle was going to be sold to a specific region.
Unfortunately, this project&amp;rsquo;s code included sensitive information, thus can not be included here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://thijsovermeer.nl/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thijsovermeer.nl/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact or follow me on these social media platforms.
   Platform URL     LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/thijs-overmeer/   GitHub: https://github.com/thijsovermeer   Gmail: thijsovermeer@gmail.com    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
